Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel PFP. Today we are going to
discuss about the ICICI Group.
Four companies are listed, out of which
ICICI Bank is performing very well. The
rest of the stocks are
not performing so well. So, in such a situation,
we are going to
discuss what we should do today. So, let's
start with ICICI Bank.
You can see a strong support around 850. On the
daily chart, we
clearly see that
it has moved up taking support from here before. If
we look at the weekly chart, there was a breakout of the all-time high here.
You can see this weekly candle
closing well, then
taking support there, it is trying to move up.
If we try to look at the monthly chart, then
here also you will be able to see
how you saw a good breakout. There was
also a train line breakout. This
four-month high also broke out. In
fact, there was a breakout of 800 here.
Then this continuous candle was seen,
then here you saw a decline.
Selling pressure appears to be building from above. The
next candle appears to be good.
If this level breaks again,
we could see a strong rally continue. However, for
now, the 800 to 850
zone appears to be an important support on the monthly chart. So,
our plan will be this:
if we want to short for the short term,
if the stock breaks this level, it could
resume its upward momentum.
We can plan accordingly.
Or, if the stock declines,
we can still
try to move higher by taking support at this level.
This level is approximately the 880 to
890 zone. We can try this zone.
If the stock moves higher from here, it is a
good thing; the momentum will remain strong.
However, if you see it breaking, the
stock could return to the 850 level. It does
n't make much sense to attempt further at 850 now because the support has weakened.  It has already taken
support here once, it took support a second
time, it took support a third time, and it has already
taken support a fourth time. Even if we
conserve it just twice,
you can see the stock moving up, taking support twice.
Currently, if there is a push here, there could be a
chance of some weakness. This support could be
seen breaking now, so we
will plan here in small quantities, and that too only
when we see a good weekly candle close.
Talking about the long term, for the long term, the zone of ₹800 to
₹850 is a very good zone
where we can think about accumulating ICICI Bank for the long term. The
second stock is ICICI Lombard.
ICICI Lombard has come below the 1600 level.
You have seen a fake breakout here.
Then there has been a
continuous decline in the stock, and the
stock is currently seen taking support at 1100.
Now you can see that there is weakness in the stock, there is
no doubt about it.  Here you
definitely saw a strong green candle
and you also saw this continuation here,
but see, there was rejection from the higher level
and this support level was
also seen breaking. The
stock is currently trading around this zone
and it has been
five-six weeks since the lower level.
You did not see any strong buying momentum.
If we look at the
monthly chart, we see that a decline was seen. The
recovery was quick and it was a
good recovery. If it had sustained here, the
stock could have gone higher, but the
1200 level was broken and
we currently see the stock trading below 1200 in the range of ₹1100 to ₹1200.
Technically,
this support here has already become weak.
If it does not cross 1200 soon, then
the chances are high that the
stock will break the 1100 level and
may try to weaken even further. ICICI
Lombard  There is no doubt that there is weakness, so
for now, we will not plan a positional trade here
until it crosses 1200. Till then, there is
no need to plan anything regarding buying.
If we talk about the long term here,
ICICI Lombard is not a bad
company, but for now, until it becomes
technically strong, I would
prefer to buy less because this is the same
level from where you
saw a rally on a closing basis.
In the Corona crash, you
also saw other low levels of ₹750-800,
but this is a good level, the price should have risen from here.
Actually, even before this, the
level of ₹1250 was a very important
level. There was a breakout here,
you saw a strong candle, so it should
not have come below this, it should have continued from here, if it
came down then it
should have continued from here, but at present,
it has gone even lower, so for now,
I would prefer to wait.
Now let's discuss ICICI.
Regarding Prudential Life Insurance, it
fell from the level of 700 to 450, a slow recovery was
seen, it went up to ₹600 but it
fell again and was seen coming down to 500, so
look here, the technical situation is still a bit weak,
how do you see, this recovery happened, there was a fall, there was a
fall, so here
you saw strong resistance around 550,
but this breakout was
seen and this is the breakout of the weekly chart, so
it should have sustained here and gone up, just like
we
saw in ICICI Bank, there was a continuous rise,
you got an all-time record, still it
went above by giving support, so this
shows strength, but if
you look at ICICI Prudential,
after going a little higher here, it should have taken support and gone up,
but it could not go up
and it came back down to 500, that was seen, so
this shows weakness, until it is
not sustained above 550, we will not expect more
bullishness here.  We won't think about it because
you had previously seen an all-time high at 550. It broke and came
back below the breakout area. So,
this wallet has become weak here. That's why
we would
n't prefer it for positional trades right now. The rise that has happened in the last two months has
also led to a bearing pattern here. This is
also not a good situation. So, if we look at this,
until it crosses above this 550 zone,
we won't short here. We wo
n't do it for short term or even for position
trades. You have seen this
train line breaking as well, so the
stock can also go down. That's why
we won't short for short term position rate.
If we want to short for long term, then
according to me, we should wait for the technicals to improve in ICICI Prudential. The
entire sector is almost
underperforming. It appears that
SBI Life is going up on the side, so
you can prefer buying there.
Those technicals are stronger in
ICICI Prudential.
For the long term, you should avoid it now. Once the technical
correction happens, you can buy it if it becomes a little stronger. The
fourth stock is ICICI Securities.
You saw a very good rally in this security as well.
First of all, I would
like to start with the Corona crash.
After the rally, this Corona crash happened, then there was
resistance here. For how many months did you see
consolation and a slide and a fall was seen. The
flag pattern was closed, it was visible.
Actually, it had been quite a long time.
Phoenix strong recovery in the flag and
this momentum continued till ₹900, but the
important support of 700 was
broken here. It would have been better if the stock had gone above this level
because the breakout
happened from the 600 area, but it came down further. The
level of 400 reached the same level from where this breakout happened.
And here you will be able to see that right now
it seems to be registering. This
big red candle was seen.
See how slow its recovery has been.
You saw this recovery after 4 months, so here
if it goes below 500, then a decline is
expected.
It's probably still on the higher side. It's
trading higher after a rally here, so
we won't be too bearish.
[Music]
Because if it sustains at 500, there's a
good chance it'll break the 550 level.
However, if it doesn't sustain at 500 and
falls, it could find
itself stuck in this range again. So,
weakness is visible here right now. The
stock is moving on a technical structural
basis. So,
what's the plan right now? If it goes above 550, we'd
prefer to buy.
We can enter for a position trade with 30% quantity.
Later, if it
breaks the 650 zone, we
can add more quantity here. This way,
we can build up for a quantity-position trade.
For the long term,
I'd prefer to see a little technical trend in the stock. If it goes
above 5:30,
we can buy.  I hope
you like this video and learn something from it.
Thank you. Stay Happy Happy
Investing.